{
    "subject": "resource/Dangerous_(film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/producer",
    "object": "resource/Harry_Joe_Brown",
    "human_readable": "The producer of the film 'Dangerous' is Harry Joe Brown.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9575018882751465,
            "question": "Is Harry Joe Brown a film producer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9464902877807617,
            "question": "Name a film produced by Harry Joe Brown."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9284279346466064,
            "question": "What is the name of the film Harry Joe Brown produced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8957648873329163,
            "question": "Is Harry Joe Brown known for producing action movies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8940721750259399,
            "question": "Has Harry Joe Brown produced any other films besides 'Dangerous'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.854999840259552,
            "question": "Who produced the film 'Dangerous'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8217656016349792,
            "question": "What role did Harry Joe Brown play in the making of 'Dangerous'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.763735830783844,
            "question": "Who is responsible for producing the movie 'Dangerous'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7137031555175781,
            "question": "What is the name of the producer of 'Dangerous'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6284099221229553,
            "question": "Besides 'Dangerous', what other projects has Harry Joe Brown worked on?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The producer of the film 'Dangerous' is Harry Joe Brown.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4096_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the producer of 'Dangerous'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4096_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is responsible for producing the movie 'Dangerous'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4096_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What role did Harry Joe Brown play in the making of 'Dangerous'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4096_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4096_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4096_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4096_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4096_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4096_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4096_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4096_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4096_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4096_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4096_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nWhile the documents mention Harry Joe Brown as a producer, they don't specifically state that he produced \"Dangerous.\"  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here's my evaluation:\n\n* File path 66.txt mentions \"Harry Joe Brown was an American film producer...\"\n* File path 15.txt mentions \"Harry Joe Brown was an American film producer...\"\n* File path 28.txt mentions \"Harry Joe Brown, who produced and directed for the screen...\"\n\nAll these files suggest that Harry Joe Brown was indeed a film producer.\n\nSo, my answer is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that Harry Joe Brown was an American film producer who produced various films, including those starring Errol Flynn and Sean Flynn. While there isn't a direct statement about him producing the film 'Dangerous', the context provided indicates his involvement in producing films which supports the inference that he could also have been involved in producing other films such as 'Dangerous'."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because there is no information provided that suggests Harry Joe Brown produced a film titled 'Dangerous'.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided about Harry Joe Brown being involved in the production of the film \"Dangerous\".",
            "category": 3
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information does not mention Harry Joe Brown producing any film titled 'Dangerous.' It focuses on his work in producing western films between 1957 and 1960 through Ranown Pictures Corp, and mentions his involvement in the production of Errol Flynn's debut films.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}